# **KELSEY BATHURST**

Kelsey.bathurst@gmail.com (613) 858-9893

#### **SUMMARY:**

I work well with people in a leadership role and I am self-motivated to work remotely. As a flight attendant I have faced challenges that I have learned from and shaped who I am today. My experience in retail and retail management provided me with a strong foundation of skills consisting of client engagement, resource management, technical aptitude and business acumen. I am ready now to develop my recently acquired full stack web development skills in the workplace.

# **EXPERIENCE:**

Air Canada, December 2019 - June 2020 Flight Attendant

Air Canada rouge, May 2013 - November 2019 Flight Attendant/Service Director

Eddie Bauer, March 2012 - November 2012 Acting Assistant Manager

Eddie Bauer, November 2007 - March 2016 Sales Associate

Sunlife Financial, Summer 2010, 2009, 2008 Support Desk Coordinator

#### **EDUCATION:**

University of Toronto, School of Continuing Studies, 2020

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

University of Ottawa, 2011

Honours Bachelor of Social Science, Major in Sociology with a Minor in History

### SKILLS:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Detail Oriented
- Node.js
- React.js

- MongoDB
- MySQL
- MySQLBootstrapCommand Line
- Microsoft Office 365
- Detail Oriented
- Strong Communicator
- Organized
  - G Suite Tools

# **CERTIFICATIONS:**

Customer Service Excellence Training - Disney Institute CPR and First Aid